TV를 볼 때에는 방을 밝게 하고 TV에서 떨어져서 봅시다.
When you're watching television, be sure to keep your room bright and keep distance from the TV!
강하게... 곱게...
Strong and gentle...
우리는 SUPER GUYS
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
메다로트: 혼
Medarot: Spirits
(Medarotto Damashī)
무적의 히로야!!
We are matchless heroes!!
태어난 그 순간이
The very moment of being born
기적을 부르는 사랑과 정의
It is the love and justice calling for a miracle
멀리 떨어져 있어도
Even when separated by distance
믿는 불꽃의 혼
The spirit of flame believes in each other
흘러라 빛나는 땀!
Flow! Sparkling sweat!
불타는 혼
Burning spirit!
둘이서라면 무한의 파워!
When there are two, infinite power shows itself!
꿈이여 펼쳐져라!
Let dreams unfold!
우리는 SUPER GUYS!
WE ARE SUPER GUYS!
고고한 히로야!!
We are lonely yet proud heroes!!
메타비!
Metabee!
좋아, 블로소메일, 메달을 부수어버려.
Good, Blossomail. Now smash the medal.
그만두라 했겠다! 유니트리스, 가라!
I told you to stop! Unitrix, go!
ギンカイ。
긴카이.
You disobeyed my orders. That'll be unforgivable, Ginkai.
내 명령을 거역했네. 용서하지 않을 거야, 긴카이.
코쿠류의 역습
Kokuryu's Revenge
(en: Once a Medafighter - Part 2)
결국 이렇게 되었네. 내가 없으면 네가 얼마나 보잘것없는 놈인지 알려 주겠어.
So this finally happened. Let me demonstrate how worthless you are without me.
가, 블로소메일. 적은 유니트리스야!
Go, Blossomail. Your enemy is Unitrix!
마스터의 명령: 유니트리스를 적으로 확정한다.
Confirming Unitrix as current enemy according to the Master's command.
쳐부수어버려, 블로소메일!
Shatter him, Blossomail!
유니트리스!
Unitrix!
긴카이! 힘으로는 어떻게 해도 블로소메일은 못 당해내! 그라피티 모드야!
Ginkai! You aren't going to stand up to Blossomail with power! Use Graffiti Mode!
그래! 그라피티 모드야, 유니트리스!
Right! To Graffiti Mode, Unitrix!
사, 사라졌어!
I- it's gone!
-위야, 긴카이!
-뭐라고?!
-Up there, Ginkai!
-What?!
유니트리스...
Unitrix...
대체 뭐하는 놈들이야? 이런 건 메다로트의 전투가 아니야!
What kind of guys are they?! This isn't a battle between Medarots!
정말로 붉은 악마야.
Truly a red devil.
긴카이, 잘 알아두는 게 좋아. 내게 거역하면 어떻게 되는지 말이야. 메달을 으깨버려, 블로소메일!
Ginkai, you'd better understand what happens if you go against me. Smash the medal, Blossomail!
도쿠스.
Dorcus.
방해해서 미안하군, 코쿠류.
Sorry to get in your way.
넌...
You're...
수수께끼의 메다로터!
The Mysterious Medarotter!
도쿠스, 그라피티 모드다!
Dorcus, to Graffiti Mode!
일어서, 블로소메일!
Stand up, Blossomail!
메다셰어즈, 발사!
Medashares, fire!
왜 그래, 블로소메일?
What's wrong, Blossomail?
양팔 파트, 기능 정지, 기능 정지.
Both arm parts stopped functioning.
팔의 대미지인가...
Damage on the arms...
운 좋네, 긴카이. 방해꾼이 나타나서.
Lucky for you, Ginkai, to have something clogging in my way.
그래도 난 집념이 강해서 말이야. 블로소메일 수리가 끝나면 바로 끝장내러 오겠어.
But you know, I'm pretty tenacious. As soon as Blossomail's repairs are done, I'll come to finish you.
유니트리스!
Unitrix!
유니트스, 괜찮아?
Unitrix, are you alright?
유니트리스!
Unitrix!
뭐가 문제야! 좀 일어나, 유니트리스!
What's wrong with you!? Stand up, Unitrix!
유니트리스! 야! 야! 유니트릭스!
Unitrix! Hey! Hey! Unitrix!
긴카이, 블로소메일은 저만큼이나 당했어. 수리하지 않으면 작동하지 않을 거야.
Ginkai, you saw what happened to Blossomail. He's not going to function without repairs.
내가 메타비하고 함께 고쳐줄 테니까, 낙심하지 마.
I'll repair him with Metabee, so don't give up.
기껏 결승전까지 왔는데, 아주 엉망이 됐네.
Too bad this happened at the very last match.
자, 참 대단한 괴롭힘을 봤지만, 일단 그건 됐고 진행하자. 자, 여러분, 어떻게 할까? 우승자는 결승전까지 이겨 온 둘로 하는 게?
What a disturbance! But let's put that away for now. Everyone, what should we do? Do both qualify as winners?
그럼 우승 상품인 아크대시와 티렐비틀은 잇키 군과 긴카이 군이 원하는 대로 나누어 갖게 하지.
Then, we'll let Ikki and Ginkai each have the prize of their choice from Arcdash and Tyrelbeetle.
아니, 우승은 긴카이야! 네 쪽이 압도적으로 우세했으니까.
No, the winner is Ginkai! You were dominantly winning on the match.
이렇게 우승한 게 되면 메타비한테 혼날 테고 말이야. 그러니까 박사님, 긴카이 집에 둘다 보내 줘요!
Moreover, if I win like this, Metabee will get angry at me.
그러냐. 그럼 그렇게 하지!
Well, if you say so!
그렇게 음양 마을 로보틀 대회 우승자는 마스크드 Q, 곧 긴카이 군으로 결정합니다!
And thus, the winner of the Ginjou City Robattle Competition is Masked Q, or Ginkai in other words!
둘 다 대미지를 상당히 입었어.
Both have taken a fair amount of damage.
나에 씨, 고칠 수 있어요?
Ms. Nae, can you fix them?
메타비는 어떻게 될 거 같은데, 유니트리스는...
I think I can deal with Metabee, but for Unitrix...
-그런!
-안됐지만 균형 제어도, 컴퓨터도,
-No way!
-I'm sorry, but balance controls, internal computer,
파트 등도, 전기 계통도 뭉그러져서 어떻게 손을 쓸 길이 없어.
parts, and electric systems are too crumpled to fix.
미안해.
I'm sorry.
유니트리스!
Unitrix!
유니트리스, 나는 지금부터 어떻게 해야 할까?
Unitrix, what should I do from now on?
코쿠류는 분명 복수하러 올 게 틀림없고.
There's no doubt Kokuryu's coming to have revenge.
그렇다고 잇키 얘들하고 친구하기도 싫고.
But I don't want to be friends with Ikki, too.
대체 어째야 할까?
What can I do?
굳이 누구하고 친구하지 않아도 된다.
You don't have to be friends with whoever.
넌 정식 로보틀에서 그만큼이나 싸움이 가능했다.
You made more than a decent fight in an official Robattle.
넌...
You...
너만큼이나 하는 놈이 코쿠류 부하인 게 이상하지.
It's really strange that you've been a follower of Kokuryu when you're that capable.
지금부터는 누구하고도 함께할 필요 없이 자신이 믿는 것을 위해 싸우면 된다.
From now on, you don't have to team up with anyone; just fight for what you believe.
믿는 것을 위해?
For what I believe?
그래, 그거다.
Yes, that's right.
긴카이, 하나 질문해도 되나.
Ginkai, may I ask you a question?
음, 어.
Er, yeah.
넌 왜 그런 비정한 코쿠류하고 함께 했나.
Why did you worked together with that cruel Kokuryu?
그건 1년 전이야. 큰 공식 로보틀 대회에 출전해서 결승 진출이 정해진 날 밤이었어.
It was a year ago. I entered a big official Robattle competition, and on the night when I was told that I'm joining finals...
다음날 결승이 있는데도 불구하고 나는 그 때의 짝 베이어니트하고 사소한 일로 크게 싸우고 말았어.
Even though we had a finals upcoming next day, I fought against my partner of that time, Bayonet, with a trivial thing.
못 참겠던 난 걔 메달을 힘으로 빼서 숲속에 봉인했어.
I couldn't stand him, so I forced his medal out of him and buried in the forest.
결국 대회에는 못 나가고 말았어. 전부터 난 로보틀을 조금 너무 잘 했었어.
I eventually couldn't join the competition. Anyway, I was pretty good at Robattles from a while ago.
그래서 아무도 로보틀 상대해주지 않았어.
For that reason, nobody faced me in Robattles.
게다가 베이어니트하고도 결별해서 난 완전 엉망이었어.
Moreover, since I parted from Bayonet, I was in a total mess.
그 때였어.
And that time...
코쿠류가 내 앞에 나타났어.
Kokuryu appeared in front of me.
안됐구나. 대회에 출전했으면 넌 분명 우승했을 텐데.
Too bad for you. You would probably have won the competition if you entered.
뭐야, 넌?
Who the heck are you?
내 이름은 코쿠류. 너 같은 최고의 메다로터를 찾고 있어.
I am Kokuryu. I've been looking for the best Medarotters like you.
최고의 메다로터?
The best Medarotters?
다른 얘들이 하는 얘들 장난같은 로보틀은 졸업하고 나하고 함께 본격적인 로보틀을 하자.
You should graduate from those childish Robattles that everyone else is doing, and join me for full-scale Robattles.
본격적인 로보틀?
Full-scale Robattles?
규칙 따위에 얽매이지 않고 진짜 힘만으로 싸워서 이기느냐 지느냐의 전투야.
It's a battle of winning or losing, using only real powers, and without rules.
건 데스페라도, 전송!
Transfer Gun Desperado!
뭐, 뭐야, 이 메다로트는?
W- what is this Medarot?
싸움에서 이기기만을 위해서 만들어진 데스 메다로트야.
It's a Death Medarot, made solely to win in battles.
데스 메다로트?
Death Medarot?
감정이 없으니까 데스 메다로터의 뜻대로 움직여. 그러니까 메다로트 사의 메다로트처럼 말대꾸도 없고, 발작도 안 해.
Since they don't have feelings, they move just as Death Medarotters want. They don't talk back or get hysterical.
그, 그거 좋네!
T- that's awesome!
어때? 내 친구가 되면 이거 줄게.
How's this? If you become my friend, then you can have this.
정말!?
Really?!
그렇지만 코쿠류가 그렇게나 비정한 놈이라고는 전혀 몰랐어! 오늘 로보틀 대회에 나가기 전까지는...
But I never thought Kokuryu was that kind of cruel guy! Well, at least until today's Robattle competition...
그 놈은 날 이용했을 뿐이야!
He simply used me, and that's all!
뭐, 그걸 안 것만으로도 오늘은 됐지 않냐.
Well, isn't it enough for today that you know that now?
그렇지. 그래도 이제 아무도 못 믿게 되어 버렸어.
Yeah, but now... I don't think I can believe anyone.
코쿠류 도련님, 수리가 완료되었습니다.
Kokuryu, the repairs are done.
좋아, 한번 보자.
Great. Let me take a look.
에, 엑스사이즈하고 싸우게 할 생각이십니까?
A- are you going to make him fight wiht Excise?
그러면 안 돼?
Can't I?
안될 건 없지만, 아무리 그래도 지금까지 써 온 엑스사이즈를...
Not that you can't, but you've been together with Excise for a while.
부숴지면 또 새 엑스사이즈 가져오면 되잖아.
If it gets destroyed, then you can just bring me a new Excise.
알겠어? 블로소메일, 엑스사이즈, 절대 봐주면 안 돼.
Blossomail and Excise, you may never go easy on each other.
해!
Start!
승부는 났어요, 도련님!
The match is set, young master!
참견하지 마. 블로소메일, 철저히 파괴해!
Don't butt in. Blossomail, destroy him thoroughly!
긴카이, 다음은 너야.
Ginkai, you're next.
기억이 지워졌다니!?
His memories are erased!?
노, 농담이죠? 동체는 잘 고쳐졌는데...
Y- you're joking! His body looks alright...
-나에 씨!
-미안해.
-Ms. Nae!
-I'm sorry.
기억 집적 회로만이 어떻게 해도 정상적으로 작동하지 않아서..
His integrated memory circuits aren't working, no matter what...
절 속여도 소용 없어요!
I'm not falling for that!
야, 메타비! 어설픈 연극 그만해!
Hey, Metabee! Stop with that sloppy act!
너 누구였냐?
Who were you, again?
메타비! 적당히 안 하면 때려눕힌다!
Metabee! If you don't quit doing that, then I'll knock you down!
메타비는 누구였냐?
Who's Metabee, again?
네 이름도 모르냐!
It's your name, of course!
그랬냐? 잊어먹었다!
It is? I forgot!
메타비...
Metabee...
잇키.
Ikki.
메타비 기억은 어떻게 못 살려요?
Is there no way to revive Metabee's memories?
할 수 있는 건 다 해 봤지만...
I've tried everything I could, but...
나에 씨, 부탁이에요! 메타비를 원래대로 해 주세요!
Please, Ms. Nae! Make Metabee just like how he was!
나에 씨는 메다로트 수리 천재잖아요!
Aren't you the genius of repairing Medarots?!
나에 씨한테 뭐라고 하지 마.
Don't blame Ms. Nae.
부탁이야.
Please.
나에 씨는 철야로 전기 요법이든 어떤 방법이든 메타비를 고치려고 했어.
Ms. Nae tried to repair Metabee using whatever method available, including electric shock, all night.
젠장! 메타비 기억은 제가 어떻게든 되살릴 거에요!
Damn! I'll revive Metabee's memories no matter what I have to do!
-메타비! 와!
-뭔데, 뭐야?
-Metabee! Come!
-What is it? What?
잇키 군...
Ikki...
-저, 갔다 올게요!
-저도!
-I'll go with him!
-Me too!
Medarot Damashii - Subtitles by Subdiver
지금부터는 누구하고도 함께할 필요 없이 자신이 믿는 것을 위해 싸우면 된다.
From now on, you don't have to team up with anyone; just fight for what you believe.
걘 그렇게 말은 했지만, 난 믿는 것 따윈 없어.
That's what he said, but I don't believe in anything.
이제 어쩐담.
What should I do?
-그만해!
-그만!
-Stop doing that!
-Stop!
둘 다 그만 좀 해!
Stop that, you two!
-용서해라!
-꺼져!
-Forgive me!
-Get lost!
뭔 일이야?
What's going on?
메타비가 기억상실이래.
Metabee lost his memories.
기억상실?
Lost his memories?
이 멍청한 메다로트가 왜 나하고의 우정이나 여러 소중한 기억을 잃었다는 거야!
You stupid Medarot! How dare you forget all the friendship and precious memories with me!?
기억이 안 나는데 어쩌라고!
Like hell I'd remember when I can't!
그렇게 간단하게 잊어먹는 게 어디 있냐! 바보야!
How dare you forget them that easily, you idiot!
적당히 해라! 너희 둘 친구잖아!
That's already enough! Aren't you friends?!
친구니까 더욱 분하단 말야!
That's why I'm even more vexing!
친구?
Friends?
형, 베이어니트, 그만해! 둘이 친구잖아!
Ginkai, Bayonet, stop that! Aren't you two friends!?
내게도 친구가 있었지. 마음 깊이 믿을 수 있는 걔가.
I did have a friend. I could really depend on him deep within my heart.
긴카이! 뭘 멍때리고 있는 거야. 둘 좀 멈춰!
Ginkai! What are you being like a fool? Stop those two!
어, 어! 임마, 작작 좀 해!
Er, right! You two, stop that!
고마워.
Thanks.
니들 덕분에 믿을 수 있는 걔가 생각났어. 나중에 보자!
Thanks to you guys, I remembered someone who I can rely on. See ya!
뭐야, 쟤?
What's his problem?
분명 여기에 묻었을 텐데.
I know I buried it here...
이걸로 1년 전에 잃어버린 신뢰와 우정을 되찾을 수 있을 거야!
With this, I'll be able to take back the trust and friendship I lost a year ago!
코, 코쿠류!
K- Kokuryu!
꽤나 찾았어. 겨우 찾았네, 긴카이.
I've been looking for you for a while. Now you show up.
어제 끝장을 내자.
Let's finish yesterday's thing.
자, 잠깐 기다려!
G- give me a moment!
사과하게?
You're apologizing?
흥! 누가 사과할까 보냐!
Hmph! In your dreams!
뭐라고?
What's that?
흥, 나는 달아나지도 숨지도 않아. 꼭 돌아와서 끝장을 내겠어.
Hmph, I'm not running away or hiding. I'll be back, and finish this business.
여기서 기다려라. 이따 보자!
Wait here. See you later!
뭐 해, 형?
What are you doing, brother?
베이어니트 찾고 있어. 분명 여기에 넣어두었을 텐데.
I'm looking for Bayonet. I know I put him inside this closet...
뭔 소리야. 베이어니트는 사촌 마크한테 줬잖아.
What are you talking about? You gave Bayonet to your cousin Mark.
그랬지...
Oh, right...
그래! 메달은 있으니까!
That's it! I still have the medal!
과연!
Let's see!
뭐, 뭐야? 내 동체가 아니야!
W- what is this? It's not my body!
역시 베이어니트다! 베이어니트!
You are Bayonet! Bayonet!
야이, 그만해, 긴카이! 니 절교하자고 했던 주제에 뭐야! 기분 나쁘게!
Hey, stop that, Ginkai! You told me that you're through with me, and what is this? That's disgusting!
베이어니트! 그 때 내가 잘못했어! 정말이야! 없던 일로 해 줘!
Bayonet! I was wrong back then! Really! Please forgive me!
자존심 높은 네가 머리를 숙이다니, 뭐, 그런 정도라면 용서하지 못할 것도 없지.
It's bizarre that you're lowering your head down, for such a prideful guy. I should forgive you then.
용서해 준 거지?! 고마워, 베이어니트!
You're forgiving me?! Thank you, Bayonet!
그러니까 기분 나쁘댔잖아!
Again, this feels disgusting!
아, 미안, 미안, 베이어니트, 아니, 오늘부터 넌 아크대시야!
Oh, sorry about that, Bayonet. No, as of today, you're Arcdash!
아크대시냐! 마음에 드네!
Arcdash, you say? I like that!
난데없지만, 아크대시, 나하고 같이 와 줘! 말도 안 되게 강한 메다로트하고 싸우게 됐어!
I know this is so sudden, but please come with me! I have to fight an unbelievably strong Medarot!
그래? 재밌겠네. 가자, 긴카이!
Hey, that sounds interesting! Let's go, Ginkai!
좋아!
Great!
잘 됐네, 형.
Good for you, brother.
잘 기다렸다, 코쿠류!
So you did wait, Kokuryu!
분명 꼬리를 내리고 돌아갔을 거라고 생각했어.
I thought you were wailing and running away.
모르는 소리 하면 안 되지. 나하고 긴카이가 어떤 최강의 콤비인데. 누가 달아날까보냐!
You were damn wrong. You don't know what kind of duo are Ginkai and me. Nobody's running away here!
그런 소리를 하는 것도 지금뿐이야. 가, 블로소메일!
Say all you like when you can. Go, Blossomail!
가라, 아크대시!
Go, Arcdash!
이 승부, 반드시 이기겠어! 준비는 됐지, 아크대시!?
I will win this match! Are you ready, Arcdash!?
물론!
Totally!
스캐터 써, 아크대시!
Use Scatter, Arcdash!
이랴!
Take this!
생각한 것보다 꽤 하잖아.
You're better than I thought.
당연하지! 이번엔 스프링클이다!
Of course he is! Use Sprinkle this time!
클러스터 실드!
Cluster Shield!
발사 그만! 방패가 말도 안 되게 딱딱하네...
Stop firing! What a tough shield!
뭐야!?
What the-!?
좋아, 한방에 끝장내. 블로소메일, 레클리스 모드로!
Alright, get rid of him at once. Blossomail, to Reckless Mode!
아야야, 임마, 이거 놔!
O- ouch! Hey! Let go of me!
젠장! 아크대시, 너도 마이티 레클리스 모드다!
Dammit! Arcdash, take Mighty Reckless Mode too!
그려!
Got it!
아크대시!
Arcdash!
끝장내, 블로소메일!
Finish him, Blossomail!
일어나! 어서, 아크대시!
Stand up! Get a grip, Arcdash!
끝이네.
It's over.
도쿠스. 또 너냐?
Dorcus. You again?
긴카이, 이 틈에 태세를 재정비해라.
Ginkai, use this moment to reorganize yourselves.
이건 내 로보틀이야! 끼어들지 마!
This is my Robattle! Don't butt in!
2대 1이어도 괜찮아. 블로소메일, 도쿠스부터 희생의 제물로 해.
Nothing changes even if it's 2 to 1. Blossomail, torment Dorcus first.
도쿠스!
Dorcus!
도, 도쿠스!
D- Dorcus!
좋아, 블로소메일. 그 김에 메달도 으깨버려!
Good job, Blossomail. Smash his medal when you can, too!
그러지 못할 테다! 가라, 아크대시!
You may not do that! Go, Arcdash!
그래!
Yeah!
쓸데없는 짓을.
How futile.
메다로트의 생명을 뭐라고 생각하는 거냐?
How much are you looking down of Medarots' lives?
긴카이, 2:1로도 승산은 없다. 네 티렐비틀을 내게 빌려줘.
Ginkai, we can't win even on 2:1 match. Lend me your Tyrelbeetle.
더이상 데스 메다로터 같은 비겁한 짓은...
I'm not doing anything cowardly like a Death Medarotter anymore!
아니, 이건 로보틀이 아니다. 생명을 건 괴물 퇴치다!
No, this is not a Robattle. It's a monster extermination done risking lives!
알겠어.
Understood.
티렐의 메다롯치야. 자!
Tyrel's Medarotch. Here!
티렐비틀 전송!
Transfer Tyrelbeetle!
티렐비틀, 마이티 레클리스 모드다!
Tyrelbeetle, to Mighty Reckless Mode!
가라, 아크대시!
Go, Arcdash!
메다로트 사의 최신형 메다로트가 다발로 달려들어 보았자 블로소메일은 못 당해내.
Even by two new type Medarots from Medarot Company, Blossomail can't be defeated.
가, 블로소메일!
Go, Blossomail!
피해를 하나도 안 입었어.
No damage has been dealt...
말도 안 돼!
No way!
이렇게는 같이 쓰러질 뿐이다. 뭔가 좋은 수 없나!?
Both are going down at this rate. Isn't there anything we can do!?
뭐야, 이거?
What's this?
티렐과 아크대시가 합체?
Tyrel and Arcdash can unite?
-이게 뭐야?
-모르지만 해 볼 가치는 있을 것 같다.
-What's this about?
-I don't know, but it definitely worth trying.
-아크대시!
-티렐비틀!
-Arcdash!
-Tyrelbeetle!
메다유나이트!
Medaunite!
메다로트가 합체?
Medarot united?
대단해, 긴카이! 몸 속에서 힘이 넘쳐흘러! 이거라면 이길 수 있어!
It's awesome, Ginkai! Power is overflowing inside my body! We can win with this!
뭐야?
What?
아무래도 날 정말 화나게 한 것 같네, 긴카이. 다음엔 반드시 갚아준다.
It seems that you made me really mad, Ginkai. You'll pay for this next time.
-해냈어.
-그래.
-We did it.
-Yes.
티렐비틀을 빌려줘서 고맙다.
Thank you for lending me Tyrelbeetle.
그건 니가 가져.
You can have him.
내 짝은 베이어니트, 아니, 아크대시 뿐이야. 걔만 있으면 돼.
My partner is Bayonet, no, Arcdash, and Arcdash only. He's more than enough.
가져 줄 거지?
Take him, will you?
그래, 소중하게 여기겠다.
Yes, I will cherish him.
젠장! 왜 기억해내지 못하는 거야!
Damn! Why can't you remember?
너무 애태우지 마, 잇키.
Don't worry too much, Ikki.
-잇키!
-어? 긴카이!
-Ikki!
-Huh? Ginkai!
내게 맡겨.
Leave him to me.
아크대시, 해라!
Arcdash, do it!
뭐, 뭔 짓이야! 놔! 이거 놓아라!
W- what are you doing!? Unhand me! Get your hands off me!
잠깐 거친 짓 할 테니까 참아라!
I'll be rough on you for a moment, so bear with me!
-거친...
-이랴!
-Rough?
-Here!
메타비!
Metabee!
내 메타비한테 뭔 짓거리야!
What are you doing to my Metabee!?
머?
The heck?
괜찮아, 메타비?
Are you alright, Metabee?
언제 원래대로 돌아올 거야.
When are you going to come back?
이 엉터리 자식!
You piece of junk!
누가 엉터리냐, 잇키?
Who's a piece of junk, Ikki?
나 알아봐?
Do you remember me?
기억이 돌아왔구나!
Your memories are back!
-메타비! 다행이야, 정말 잘 됐어!
-대체 뭐가!
-Metabee! What a relief! It's good to have you back!
-What are you talking about!?
너 정말 바보라니까!
You're truly an idiot!
게다가 왜 나 거꾸로야! 어서 제대로 세워!
Forget that; why am I upside down!? Get me positioned right!
아침은 싫어하지만 어느 날 돌연
Mornings are not my favorite, but someday on a sudden
자명종 울리기 전에 일어났어
I woke up before my alarm clock rings
내 가슴이 메어지게 괴로워
My wringing heart is so troubled
슬픈 만큼 당신은 연상의 사람
As much as I'm sad, you are older than me
쭉 보고 있어도 닿지 않아
Gazing at you isn't getting me through
키하고 하트
Height and heart
빛나는 미소는
Is the shining smile
우러러 볼 뿐만인 태양?
nothing more than a sun that I admire?
Don't mind 신경쓰지 마
Don't mind, don't make it let you down
My girl 쏘아올리기 전에
To my girl, before you make a dash,
Fight mind 무기력함에 져 버린다면
have a fighting mindset! If you lose to timorousness,
사랑은 잡을 수 없어
you cannot catch the love
차회예고
Preview for Next Episode
최신 비행형 데스 메다로트 플라이팔콘이 메타비를 등에 태운 채로 제어 불능하게 된다.
A new flying type Death Medarot, Flyfalcon, is out of control, with Metabee on his back.
하늘을 그것도 맹렬한 속도로 질주하는 플라이팔콘의 자폭 장치가 작동한다.
On top of that, while Flyfalcon is in one intense flight, his self-destruction timer starts to tick.
남은 시간은 앞으로 100분.
They have only 100 minutes remaining.
고도 만 피트를 무대로 한 결사의 메타비 구출 작전이 시작된다..
Metabee rescue plan begins, over 10,000 ft. on the air.
과연 잇키는 메타비를 무사히 구해낼 수 있을 것인가!
Will Ikki manage to rescue Metabee safe and sound?
메다로트 혼의 다음 이야기! 하늘에서 전투!
Next time on Medarot Damashii! Battle in Sky!
타올라라, 뜨거운 혼이여!
Let the hot spirit burn up!